Yee N.

Sydney, New South Wales, Australia

Summary

I'm a Junior Web Developer, excited to embark on a six-month coding bootcamp at Coder Academy.

I'm currently located in sunny Sydney, originally from Borneo and having lived in New Zealand for almost 10 years. Before becoming a dev, I had a successful and rewarding career in the accounting and banking industry in both New Zealand and Australia.

In my free time, I enjoy reading and spending time outdoors such as going on a hike or hanging out at the beach. I'm also an enthuasiastic home cook and foodie.

Experience



Student

Coder Academy

Aug 2020 - Present (1 month +)

Personal Banker

TSB Bank

Jul 2016 - Apr 2017 (10 months)

- Help customers manage their bank accounts and finances.
- Advise clients on financial services and resolve issues.
- Present financial products and services to existing and prospective customers.



Personal Banker

ANZ

Jun 2014 - Jan 2016 (1 year 8 months)

- Process and determine a decision on lending applications such as overdraft, credit card and personal loan.
- Provide sound financial advice to help customers achieve their financial goals.
- Promote various banking products to customers which will suit their needs while contributing to the growth of bank's revenue.

Education



🔼 Coder Academy

Diploma of Information Technology

2020 - 2021



University of Canterbury

Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com.), Accounting

2008 - 2010



University of Canterbury

Foundation Studies

2007 - 2007



Kuching High School

Malaysian Certificate of Education

2002 - 2006